Fight for the sky
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
I can't stop the overflowing emotions
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
The illusions we hold so dear
Just revolution
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Fear of the scar that won't disappear
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Won't stop the ruthless passage of time
susumeyo aru ga mama
Go forth, the way you are
Let's burst up!
ima koso kawaru toki
Now is the time for change
Let's boost up!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
The sound of the bell of revolution
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Resounds far and wide
To be the soldier
mou koko ni wa irarenai
We can't stay here any longer
To be the soldier
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Cut through the wind, live your life
hiryuu no gotoku
Like a flying dragon
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
As the beginning draws near, become a legend
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Release yourself, fly ahead
inochi wo tagirasete
Overflow with life
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
The world that waits for a chosen one is over! New age!
m 486.37 475.17 b 480.71 475.17 473.8 473.47 475.03 481.92 475.25 483.41 478.68 482.98 477.15 485.29 476.96 485.57 473.37 485.29 473.23 485.29 473.35 485.29 469.5 485.52 469.32 485.29 467.82 483.4 470.78 483.13 470.92 482.64 472.4 477.04 474.76 471.31 476.45 465.7 477.53 462.1 478.81 451.73 482.39 450.82 488.97 449.15 492.14 474.83 494.99 479.86 495.7 481.12 498.78 483.94 497.94 485.29 497.55 485.92 489.88 485.43 489.34 485.29 488.79 485.15 486.19 485.7 485.92 485.29 484.92 483.73 487.66 482.38 487.68 482.84 487.59 480.16 487.2 478.05 486.37 475.17 m 485.56 472.56 b 484.23 468.15 483.17 462.88 481.24 458.92 479.98 463.47 478.72 468.01 477.46 472.56 480.16 472.56 482.86 472.56 485.56 472.56 m 533.44 461.31 b 531.38 449.2 521.47 453.21 519.76 463.29 518.96 468.01 519.19 485.31 527.87 483.07 530.93 482.27 531.72 479.78 530.74 476.65 530.23 475.02 527.7 472.58 527.73 472.33 527.92 470.21 538.78 470.5 539.38 472.33 539.51 472.71 537.39 474.37 537 475.75 536.35 478.01 537.65 480.45 536.33 482.38 529.93 491.77 515.33 483.62 512.92 475.57 509.94 465.59 513.67 452.69 525.13 450.98 529.68 450.3 533.44 451.04 535.32 454.48 536.65 456.92 537.35 461.74 533.44 461.31 m 551.35 462.21 b 551.35 467.49 549.97 474.62 551.35 479.68 551.88 481.6 554.18 484.78 553.67 485.29 552.95 486.02 544.74 485.67 543.76 485.29 539.48 483.65 543.58 484.73 544.26 482.75 545.28 479.84 544.71 475.65 544.69 472.61 544.69 471.76 544.95 470.22 544.69 469.35 544.97 470.29 542.08 462.72 541.81 465.81 542.08 462.64 548.59 462.19 551.35 462.21 m 547.75 451.68 b 552.43 451.68 552.87 459.58 547.75 459.55 543.03 459.53 542.67 451.68 547.75 451.68 m 565.44 465.53 b 567.54 462.64 576.16 459.25 575.56 465.99 574.99 472.41 568.74 461.07 565.57 468.41 564.65 470.53 564.96 477.53 565.57 479.68 566.98 484.63 571.06 484.04 565.15 485.29 563.72 485.59 558.84 485.91 557.55 485.29 555.51 484.32 556.86 485.1 557 483.3 556.94 484.11 558.93 479.45 558.96 479.32 559.4 477.38 558.97 474.68 558.96 472.73 558.95 471.26 559.39 468.76 558.89 467.38 558.2 465.47 555.85 466.5 556.26 464.46 556.41 463.68 566.95 458.52 565.44 465.53 m 577.32 483.36 b 582.48 483.36 580.64 462.76 580.24 458.81 579.86 455.08 576.93 453.52 578.31 452.08 578.54 451.84 586.03 449.93 586.47 450.24 587.35 450.83 586.46 451.81 586.86 452.76 590.02 460.28 584.88 471.52 586.86 479.51 587.83 483.44 591.01 483.92 587.56 485.29 585.06 486.29 577.03 486.42 577.32 483.36 m 592.98 461.67 b 594.58 460.46 596.07 458.64 596.17 456.54 591.59 461.12 590.62 445.54 597.9 451.86 601.16 454.68 596.27 465.27 592.98 461.67 m 603.55 478.05 b 604.44 481.27 609.85 487.15 612.78 481.9 615.38 477.22 605.61 474.7 603.78 471.95 600.54 467.09 603.5 463.14 608.79 461.99 610.35 461.65 613.69 461.4 615.32 462.12 618.96 463.72 618.1 464.54 618.9 468.33 616.09 469.02 614.04 460.49 609.74 464.5 605.52 468.44 615.13 471.34 617.19 473.49 622.26 478.8 619.35 484.53 612.53 485.73 610.39 486.11 604.22 486.23 602.56 484.55 601.29 483.25 600.5 478 603.55 478.05 m 644.63 470.58 b 642.32 466.26 640.4 460.93 637.4 457.08 634.17 452.94 631.38 452.23 637.5 451.45 638.87 451.28 644.37 450.69 645.52 451.45 648.68 453.54 644.38 452.57 644.28 454.65 644.11 457.98 648.72 464.39 650.39 466.93 651.96 463.62 655.9 458.33 655.93 454.56 655.94 453.55 652.39 453.28 654.22 451.45 654.57 451.1 660.82 451.27 661.11 451.45 663.36 452.93 660.05 454.91 658.36 457.34 656.02 460.71 652.86 466.29 651.82 470.25 651.19 472.64 650.8 479.6 652.07 481.87 652.87 483.29 657.64 482.91 655.56 485.29 655.08 485.83 650.86 485.29 650.02 485.29 648.16 485.29 643.32 486.14 641.7 485.29 638.71 483.73 642.18 484.14 642.79 483 644.81 479.2 644.63 475.55 644.63 470.58 m 682.93 480.21 b 675.91 492.94 658.89 483.11 662.11 470.17 665.43 456.87 683.06 460.62 683.06 473.82 678.29 473.82 673.52 473.82 668.75 473.82 668.75 478.37 670.22 483.96 675.83 483.25 679.24 482.81 679.96 478.26 682.93 480.21 m 676.31 471.75 b 676.31 462.29 668.75 462.33 668.75 471.75 671.27 471.75 673.79 471.75 676.31 471.75 m 699.67 468.51 b 699.67 465.83 698.47 463.46 695.51 464.05 692.97 464.56 693.63 466.97 691.94 468 689.37 469.57 686.48 469.03 687.5 465.47 688.3 462.65 693.32 462.02 695.45 461.88 703.11 461.34 705.88 464.34 706.28 471.46 706.38 473.18 705.22 485.32 708.98 483 710.2 489.81 701.09 483.14 699.98 483.09 695.82 482.9 692.05 489.3 687.43 483.47 679.01 472.85 700.72 473.67 699.67 468.51 m 699.67 472.51 b 696.87 473.39 692.71 475.09 692.96 478.77 693.15 481.49 695.15 484.05 698.18 482.12 700.94 480.37 699.67 475.44 699.67 472.51 m 720.28 465.53 b 722.38 462.64 731 459.25 730.4 465.99 729.84 472.41 723.58 461.07 720.41 468.41 719.5 470.53 719.8 477.53 720.41 479.68 721.82 484.63 725.91 484.04 719.99 485.29 718.56 485.59 713.68 485.91 712.39 485.29 710.35 484.32 711.7 485.1 711.84 483.3 711.78 484.11 713.77 479.45 713.8 479.32 714.24 477.38 713.81 474.68 713.8 472.73 713.79 471.26 714.23 468.76 713.73 467.38 713.04 465.47 710.7 466.5 711.1 464.46 711.25 463.68 721.8 458.52 720.28 465.53 m 741.56 465.63 b 744.47 462.09 750.82 459.9 754.46 463.85 756.83 466.43 756 472.16 756.01 475.38 756.02 477.99 756.53 480.6 756.74 482.92 756.8 483.54 759.51 483.31 758.3 485.29 758.24 485.4 755.24 485.35 755.46 485.29 753.24 485.92 748.13 485.77 747.32 484.33 747.56 484.75 749.28 479.68 749.39 478.61 749.7 475.84 749.85 472.18 749.39 469.4 748.56 464.3 744.35 462.72 741.56 468.45 740.55 470.53 741.38 476.07 741.56 478.26 741.66 479.34 743.33 484.48 743.54 483.36 742.96 486.48 740.37 485.29 736.93 485.29 736.58 485.29 732.9 485.69 732.59 485.29 731.16 483.42 733.6 483.84 733.69 483.25 734.51 477.99 734.99 472.34 734.48 466.41 734.36 465.05 731.72 466.87 732.2 464.45 732.3 463.98 737.52 462.49 738.37 462.61 740.8 462.96 742.31 460.81 741.56 465.63 m 770 462.21 b 770 467.49 768.62 474.62 770 479.68 770.53 481.6 772.83 484.78 772.32 485.29 771.6 486.02 763.4 485.67 762.42 485.29 758.13 483.65 762.23 484.73 762.92 482.75 763.93 479.84 763.36 475.65 763.34 472.61 763.34 471.76 763.6 470.22 763.34 469.35 763.62 470.29 760.73 462.72 760.46 465.81 760.73 462.64 767.24 462.19 770 462.21 m 766.4 451.68 b 771.09 451.68 771.52 459.58 766.4 459.55 761.69 459.53 761.32 451.68 766.4 451.68 m 784.27 465.63 b 787.18 462.08 793.53 459.9 797.16 463.85 799.54 466.43 798.7 472.16 798.71 475.38 798.72 477.99 799.24 480.6 799.44 482.92 799.5 483.54 802.22 483.31 801.01 485.29 800.94 485.4 797.95 485.35 798.16 485.29 795.95 485.92 790.84 485.77 790.03 484.33 790.26 484.75 791.98 479.68 792.1 478.61 792.4 475.84 792.55 472.18 792.1 469.4 791.26 464.3 787.06 462.72 784.27 468.45 783.26 470.53 784.08 476.07 784.27 478.26 784.36 479.34 786.04 484.48 786.25 483.36 785.66 486.48 783.07 485.29 779.64 485.29 779.29 485.29 775.6 485.69 775.3 485.29 773.86 483.42 776.3 483.84 776.39 483.25 777.22 477.99 777.7 472.34 777.18 466.41 777.06 465.05 774.42 466.87 774.91 464.45 775 463.98 780.23 462.49 781.08 462.61 783.51 462.96 785.02 460.81 784.27 465.63 m 823.42 464.95 b 826.82 468.22 826.04 473.85 822.59 476.68 818.75 479.81 815.21 477.14 811.44 478.24 801.87 481.01 818.24 482 820.23 482.37 830.82 484.32 829.03 494.42 819.71 496.95 815.98 497.96 809.27 498.39 805.87 496.16 800.62 492.72 803.08 488 808.16 486.24 802.07 484.44 804.26 479.33 808.39 477.15 801.59 473.33 804.26 464.56 810.66 462.37 816.13 460.49 822.02 463.27 827.78 462.39 827.96 463.06 827.95 464.77 827.78 465.45 826.42 465.29 824.72 465.39 823.42 464.95 m 810.59 487.05 b 800.83 494.01 820.59 499.94 822.21 491.59 823.34 485.84 814.27 487.05 810.59 487.05 m 815.05 476.7 b 820.57 476.7 820.43 463.88 815 463.87 809.51 463.86 809.43 476.7 815.05 476.7
How long are you going to keep running, Black Hero?
I thought you were supposed to stop me.
The Giant is right there in front of Crossfeed!
You people fell right into our trap.
If my intel is right, you won't be able to use Bahamut
for more than a few minutes in your current state!
So that's why you lured me into it!
Your time should be just about up.
End of the line for you people!
Howling Roar!
A meaningless effort!
That arm...
It's not Bahamut's!
How?!
How do you have two Bahamuts?!
The other Machine Dragon was a Wyvern made to look like Bahamut.
I had a backup plan in case
something went south.
Why you little...
That's the fifth ruin,
commonly known as the Giant.
We can't have an All Dragons Battle
with this at our doorstep.
Airi! Do you read me?
Lux! You're all right?
Thank goodness.
Yes. How about you guys?
Lux, I have something to tell you.
It's about Miss Lisha.
Long time no see, Your Highness.
Saniya!
Can you see that?
They're an eyesore.
Make them disappear.
Yes, Creator.
As you can see, it's only a matter of time
before the new kingdom falls.
Miss Hayes has ordered you, as a princess,
to serve as a negotiator,
so that we can avoid needless casualties in this war.
I'll never let people like you have this kingdom!
No need put on a tough front for me.
I know you're a traitor who once sided with the former empire.
But he accepted me despite that.
He said he'll fight by my side.
I hear there's something interesting to see
on the stomach of the princess.
Disrobe her so we can have a look.
Please, save me, Lux.
Lux!
You again?!
Lux Arcadia.
Fine, then.
There are plenty of others we could take hostage.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Miss Lisha.
I... I'm too ashamed to face you.
I lost control in the All Dragons Battle,
and failed our kingdom.
That was a trap set by Hayes.
I know!
But that doesn't mean anything!
Because of me, the efforts of everyone who fought for the kingdom—
your efforts—all went to waste.
Thank you for thinking of me.
But it's okay.
Even if no one in this kingdom or in this world accepts me,
so long as you accept me, I can fight.
I need your strength, Miss Lisha.
So that this time,
I can protect us and this kingdom.
Miss Lisha.
Let's go, Lux.
I'm warning you.
This fight has already been decided.
The new kingdom's army
is to surrender immediately.
Anyone who doesn't heed this warning will be exterminated.
So someone managed to
survive our previous attack.
Fafnir?
Makes sense.
She used her premonition ability, Wise Blood.
Turn all cannons to her,
so she has nowhere to hide!
What?!
The monster girl, huh?
Get lost, maggots!
You can't stop my giant with that!
All you can do is watch as I destroy Crossfeed!
Grovel before the name of God!
Thresher!
So the dishonored princess has come
to show more of her disgrace.
Shut up!
You'll pay for what you've done to me and to this kingdom!
Don't get too full of yourself.
Did you think you could stop the Giant with such a simple trick?
Lux!
Miss Lisha.
I'm going to strengthen Tiamat's Thresher using Reload on Fire.
Is that even—
It is possible!
The two of us can do it.
All right!
We're doing it!
Let's go, Lux!
Yes!
Reload on Fire!
Grovel before the names of God and the dragon king!
Thresher!
Phi!
Krulcifer!
Freezing Cannon!
Creator, we have been rendered immobile.
It will take a little over ten minutes
to restore optimal running conditions.
Good work, Lux!
But the rebel army is still inside the city.
All right, then.
Phi, Krulcifer, please deal with the
Gargoyles and rebel forces inside the city.
Miss Lisha and I are going inside the Giant.
All right.
Be careful, Lu.
Thanks. I will.
Lux.
It's time to settle this.
Yes.
I've never felt like this before.
Having you by my side inspires unexpected confidence in me.
Look out!
That split the city in half!
Sorry for the late introduction.
This is my Divine Raiment Machine Dragon,
Níðhöggr!
Who are you, wench?
Silence, aristocrat swine!
You have no right to question me.
Obey us, or be exterminated.
Celistia?
I came to get back at...
No. I came to take responsibility for my previous failure.
What can you hope to accomplish, Celis?
I used to think I understood you,
but I was wrong.
That's why I'm going to settle this now!
Astral Rain!
Stop!
Who in the world are you
and what are you fighting for?
I'll tell you... as I hold your execution!
What's wrong, princess?
Is that all you can do by yourself?
Wait...
Where's Bahamut?
Could he have gone to
the Giant's control room?!
Seven Heads, huh?
You're not worth the Black Hero's time.
I can take care of you by myself!
Scoundrel!
You pathetic excuse for a princess!
I need to find an entrance.
I've been expecting you, Master.
Unfortunately, it seems you
have not changed your mind.
In that case, I'll have to defeat you, Master,
and restore the empire under your sister.
I'm sorry, but I seem to have
found a reason to fight you too.
And what is that?
To save you.
Why are you hellbent on restoring the empire?
As I explained before, I wish to honor
the pact I made for my brother.
Then why was your brother killed?
That's an curious thing to ask,
given these circumstances.
I think I need to know the answer.
As the last prince of the former empire.
The one who killed my brother
was not from the empire.
Back then, the castle was
surrounded while I was absent.
On the condition that my brother be spared,
I entered the empire's service.
However, our senior statesmen, who had given up
fighting in the face of the empire's military power,
blamed my brother to protect themselves.
They decapitated him and
offered his head to the empire.
I was filled with regret.
But that must have been our fate.
My brother had fulfilled his fate as monarch,
and I decided to devote myself to the fate,
by keeping my pact with the empire.
You're wrong!
I know a girl who defies fate,
no matter how cruel, and keeps fighting.
I've been watching her fight on,
despite her circumstances,
without becoming conceited over being called a princess.
So...
The time for getting to know each other is over.
Let's finish this, Master.
What was that?
Let's call it "Etching Strike."
Consciousness is like breathing.
No matter how much you concentrate, there are moments of discontinuity.
I aim for that moment to strike.
Do you understand now, Master?
I'm doing this to keep my pact with the empire.
Please don't think ill of me.
My fight is not over!
Even though the empire was destroyed, it still goes on!
Just like you and your brother,
who pursued your ideals!
How did you...
I managed to read your movements
at the last moment.
Because you gave yourself to emotions.
I can't believe I, the heartless,
still had that in me.
In the past, I tried to save this kingdom and failed.
I wanted to save as many people as I could.
That's why I had the determination to destroy the Arcadia Empire.
I'm appalled.
To choose to destroy your own kingdom in order to save it...
Looks like I've misunderstood you, Master.
You've been fighting alone all this time
for the sake of the Arcadia Empire.
What's causing these tremors?
Preparing to execute final order.
What are you planning to do, Hayes?!
It's your fault for making me angry.
Now, I hope you'll be relieved to know,
you and the people of the new kingdom,
whom you tried to protect,
are about to die together.
Sorry I took so long to
come back, Miss Lisha.
Y-You sure took your sweet time.
Don't make me worry like that.
I don't have much time left in Bahamut.
Right! Let's teach her a lesson!
Can you really?
Creator, thirty seconds to royal capital obliteration.
You villain! What have you done?!
Whatever you planned to do, it's too late now.
I've obtained great power.
The time has come once more for
the world to submit to my bloodline!
Ten seconds to royal capital obliteration.
Nine.
Eight.
Clink. Good night.
I'll leave the rest to you, Master.
She betrayed me!
Then I'll destroy this kingdom
with my own hands!
Your time is over!
Reload on Fire.
We don't need someone to rule over us with force.
Miss Lisha fights to protect everyone.
I'll put my trust in her!
Lux...
New Kingdom of Atismata
Kingdom Founding Festival, Final Day
People of the kingdom,
greetings on this lovely evening.
As princess of this kingdom, I'm here to conclude
the festivities with gratitude to our military forces.
I have today chosen a personal knight.
And it is this man
who you all know as the
prince of the former empire,
Lux Arcadia.
After spending time to get to know him,
I've found him to be reliable in both combat skills and personality.
I wish not for the kingdom I am to build
to be bound by the past.
We should accept past
failures and transgressions,
and set our sights on building the best future possible.
Choosing this man as my knight is proof of that.
So, while I don't expect you to accept this right away,
I do ask you to judge us by
what we do from here on out.
See if what I strive for is truly just.
That is what I ask of you.
Nicely done, Miss Lisha.
You were splendid.
I was so nervous.
I was happy that you accepted me
with your speech.
W-Were you?
Yes.
That's why I'll—
I'll work for the people of this kingdom and this school.
S-So about that, Lux.
Now that you're officially my knight,
We should get to know each even better.
You looked great up there.
As befitting my fiancé.
You're the pride of our knight squadron.
I was so excited.
Lu, you're sweating.
You're all wet.
In the nook of night where even trees sleep, in a cranny of the world
kusaki mo nemuru yoru no sumi de sekai no fushi de
Well, I was a bit nervous.
It's not good for your health
to stay like that.
I hear the breath of someone asleep nearby, close my eyes, and prick up my ears
neiki ni sotto mimi wo tatete hitomi wo tojiru
Master, shall I help you change clothes?
A warm seed of life near my neck
kubisuji ni futto atatakana inochi no tsubu ga
Yoruka?!
And if you so desire,
I'll also take care of you at night.
is screaming that it's there, in a voice without voice
koko ni iru tte sakenderun da koe naki koe de
Wha— What are you saying?!
I shall serve you in any way I can, Master,
as long as you strive to build your ideal kingdom.
If we can be reborn endlessly
umarekawaretara owarinaki you ni
Let's take such forms
kimi ga nodo wo itamenakute
Oh, now we have another
member for Luxy's Lovelies.
that we won't need to scream so hard to be heard
sumu you na sugata ni narou
You're beyond hopeless.
Now we're traveling, the two of us. How far can we go?
sashiatatte futari tabi doko made arukeru
Yes. You're the worst.
What?!
Lux! Please restrain yourself!
Let's go as far as we can, matching each other's pace
ikeru toko made ikou hohaba awasete
Not you too, Airi.
Hey, Lux!
You have me, but you still...
And when we finally get to the end of the path, the two of us
tsukiatatte futari tabi koko made kureba
Answer, Lux!
Who do you love?!
Let's become trees and stay there
kigi ni natte tachitsukusou
Me, of course. Right, Lux?
Even in the next world, let's keep sleeping there
raise ni natte mo zutto koko de nemurou
To tell the truth, I've been in love—
Go Celis!
I'm hungry.
Come, Master, I'll give you an heir.
The two of us, let's sleep for eternity
futari nemurou towa ni
Lux, what about me?!
Then, me too!
Yes.
Give me a break!